We got this new deal today
The work is at the Infinity heights
apartments near Yelahanka
So, here's the plan…
On the first floor, at this house…
This figurine…
On the last floor, at this house…
This painting
We are not concerned with
what those things are worth
Our job is…
To break into these houses…
…and steal those things
But…
How will you all get inside the building?
We will just have to jump
over the back wall
But…
What about the cameras there…?
Huh…?
As far as I know…
Very few people live there
and most of the houses are vacant
That’s right…
Also, there’s just one watchman there
However, there’s a camera on every floor…
But no one will be watching the live feed…
That means…
Just covering our faces is enough…
Yeah, you cover your face first…
It's so ugly to look at…
You son of a b…
(Laughs)
Bhaira…
You go get the car ready
It is 4:30 pm now
We will reach there around 5
Listen…
Do not forget to…
Change the number plate too…
Yeah…
This is the key to the house
where that figurine is.
No one will be in that house today
So, it will be an easy job to
find and steal it
But I did not get the key to
the house on the last floor
So, Rudra…
You will have to break the lock of that house
Hmm…
But…
There will be a guy inside who lives there
An old guy…
But he is completely paralyzed…
That means he cannot move or speak
He won’t be of any trouble to us then
We must be careful nevertheless
So, Bhaira will be in the car…
I will go to the house on the first floor
And I will go to the last floor and break the lock
What will you be doing?
On the last floor…
There is a storeroom
I was told that…
There might be an old book
named Vivartha there
And I was ordered to get that
if I could find it
So, I will go there
It's Bhaira…
He texted that the car is ready
Fine…
Let’s go get this done
Hmm…
What time is it?
It's 5:15 now
By 5:45…
Let's finish the job
and get back in the car
Be careful guys
We always are
Come on… It's clear
Won’t anyone be there
looking after that Oldman?
No, I was told that a nurse visits him…
But only after 7 pm
Is this the house?
Yes…
I'll break it in a few seconds…
What might this trash be worth?
♪♪
♪ Give three lives ♪
(Laughs)
Wants me to give three lives…
Yeah, come on, I'll give you…
Huh…
It’s just the wind…
Unlock the door…
Did you find the thing?
Yes, I did
Show me the thing…
NO… I won’t show you MY THING.
Is it not done yet?
Just give me a minute…
I’ll get it done… Just a minute…
I did not find any book…
That storeroom is like a ruin…
There is nothing there
How long are you going to take?
Finally, you did it!
How did this open up?
Oh my god, he looks so creepy…
Just ignore him
Didn’t you say there’s some painting here?
Where is it?
I don’t know…
It may be somewhere inside
What's wrong?
Didn’t you say he was paralyzed
and he cannot move?
How the hell is he sitting now?
I have no idea…
Let’s get out of here first
Let's get the hell out of here
How can we leave him like that?
Let me help him…
Sir…!?
Sir… Sir…
Are you alright?
Rudra…
What happened?
♪♪♪
Hey!
♪
What…?
Weren’t they supposed to be back by now?
They'll be back soon…
The time is 6:30 now…
Go back and check on them once…
Huh..?
I won’t jump over that wall again…!
If you are so worried…
Go there yourself
You are good for nothing..
You gluttonous ass
Rudra…!?
Rudra?
What's wrong?
Talk to me…!
What are they still doing there…?
Huh...!?
Oh, Thank God!
What the hell did you do…?
Did you kill him…?
Weird things happened here…
Please let’s get out of here first…
You killed him…
And now you are bullshitting me? huh?
No…
What are you going to do now?
Kill me too…?
I said NO …
Is it 6:50 already?
Why haven’t they come back yet?
♪  Will you give me three lives?  ♪
(Laughs)
Come on… I'll give you…
You agreed to give me three lives…
You have given two until now…
What's remaining is…
ONE LIFE...